<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.ksnakeduel.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Ormspel</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKSnakeDuelxx</name>
  <summary>Tron-like Game</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Joc a l'estil del Tron</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Joc a l'estil del Tron</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Hra podobná tronu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Juego semejante a Tron</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Tronachtig spel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Jogo Semelhante ao Tron</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Tron-liknande spel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Гра, подібна до Tron</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxTron-like Gamexx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      KSnakeDuel is a simple Tron-Clone. You can play KSnakeDuel against the computer or a friend.
      The aim of the game is to live longer than your opponent. To do that, avoid running into a
      wall, your own tail and that of your opponent.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KSnakeDuel és un clon senzill del Tron. Pots jugar al KSnakeDuel contra l'ordinador o un amic. L'objectiu del joc és viure més que el contrari. Per fer-ho, evita córrer per una paret, la pròpia cua i la del contrari.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KSnakeDuel és un clon senzill del Tron. Pots jugar al KSnakeDuel contra l'ordinador o un amic. L'objectiu del joc és viure més que el contrari. Per fer-ho, evita córrer per una paret, la pròpia cua i la del contrari.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KSnakeDuel is een eenvoudig Tron-kloon. U kunt KSnakeDuel spelen tegen de computer of een vriend. Het doel van het spel is langer dan uw tegenstander in leven te blijven. Om dit te bereiken moet u een botsing met een muur, uw eigen staart en de staart van uw tegenstander vermijden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KSnakeDuel é um clone simples do Tron. Poderá jogar o KSnakeDuel contra o computador ou com um amigo. O objectivo do jogo é sobreviver mais tempo que o seu adversário. Para o fazer, evite bater contra uma parede, a sua própria cauda ou a do seu adversário.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Ormspelet är en enkel klon av Tron. Man kan spela ormspelet mot datorn eller mot en vän. Spelets mål är att överleva längre än motspelaren. För att göra det, undvik att träffa en vägg, din egen kropp eller motspelaren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KSnakeDuel — це проста гра «дуель змій» (Tron). Грати у KSnakeDuel можна або з комп’ютерним гравцем, або з другом (подругою). Метою гри є вижити у грі довше, ніж ваш суперник. Щоб зробити це, уникайте контакту зі стінами, хвостом вашої змійки або вашим опонентом.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKSnakeDuel is a simple Tron-Clone. You can play KSnakeDuel against the computer or a friend. The aim of the game is to live longer than your opponent. To do that, avoid running into a wall, your own tail and that of your opponent.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=ksnakeduel</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=ksnakeduel</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://kde.org/images/screenshots/ksnakeduel.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>ksnakeduel</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
