<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.ksnakeduel</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <developer id="org.kde">
    <name translate="no">KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <name>KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">مبارزة الأفعى</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KPojedynekWęży</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="sa">KSnakeDuel इति</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">К‑змијски-двобој</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-Latn">K‑zmijski-dvoboj</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">К‑змијски-двобој</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">K‑zmijski-dvoboj</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Ormspel</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">K Yılan Düellosu</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKSnakeDuelxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">KSnakeDuel</name>
  <summary>Tron-like Game</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">لعبة شبيه بترون</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Joc a l'estil del Tron</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Joc a l'estil de Tron</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Hra podobná Tronu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Tron-lignende spil</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Tron-ähnliches Spiel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Παιχνίδι τρον</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Tron-like Game</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Ludo simila al Tron</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Juego similar a Tron</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Troni moodi mäng</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Tron antzeko jokoa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Tron-mainen peli</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Jeu dans le style de Tron</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Xogo similar a Tron</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">משחק דמוי טרון</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Tron-szerű játék</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Permainan Seperti Tron</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Gioco simile a Tron</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">Tron-ის მსგავსი თამაში</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">트론 게임</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">„Tron“ līdzīga spēle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Tronachtig spel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Tron-liknande spel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Gra typu Tron</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Jogo Semelhante ao Tron</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Jogo no estilo Tron</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Игра в стиле «Tron»</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sa">ट्रोन्-सदृशः गेमः</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Hra ako Tron</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Igra podobna Tronu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Игра налик на трон</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-Latn">Igra nalik na tron</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Игра налик на трон</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Igra nalik na tron</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Tron-liknande spel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Tron benzeri Oyun</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Гра, подібна до Tron</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxTron-like Gamexx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">类 Tron 游戏</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">類似 Tron 的遊戲</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      KSnakeDuel is a simple Tron-Clone. You can play KSnakeDuel against the computer or a friend.
      The aim of the game is to live longer than your opponent. To do that, avoid running into a
      wall, your own tail and that of your opponent.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">مبارزة الأفعى هي لعبة بسيط شبيهة بلعبة ترون. يمكنك لعب مبارزة الأفعى ضد الحاسوب أو ضد صديق. الهدف من اللعبة هو أن تعيش أطول مدة من خصمك. للفعل ذلك، تجنب الاصطدام بالحائط أو بذيل خصمك.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KSnakeDuel és un clon senzill del Tron. Pots jugar al KSnakeDuel contra l'ordinador o un amic. L'objectiu del joc és viure més que el contrari. Per a fer-ho, evita córrer per una paret, la cua pròpia i la del contrari.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">KSnakeDuel és un clon senzill de Tron. Pots jugar a KSnakeDuel contra l'ordinador o un amic. L'objectiu del joc és viure més que el contrari. Per a fer-ho, evita córrer per una paret, la cua pròpia i la del contrari.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">KSnakeDuel er en simpel klon af Tron. Du kan spille KSnakeDuel mod computeren eller en ven. Målet med spillet er er at overleve længere end din modstander. For at gøre det skal du undgå at køre ind i væggen, din egen hale eller din modstanders.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KSnakeDuel ist eine einfache Kopie des Spiels „Tron“.Sie können KSnakeDuel gegen den Rechner oder einen Freund spielen. Das Ziel ist länger zu leben als der Gegner. Dazu darf man weder in eine Mauer noch in den eigenen oder gegnerischen „Körper“ rennen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το KSnakeDuel είναι ένας απλός κλώνος τρον. Μπορείς να παίξεις KSnakeDuel με τον υπολογιστή ή με έναν φίλο. Ο στόχος του παιχνιδιού είναι να επιζήσεις περισσότερο από τον αντίπαλο. Για να τα καταφέρεις, απόφυγε την επαφή με τοίχο, με την ουρά σου ή με την ουρά του αντιπάλου.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KSnakeDuel is a simple Tron-Clone. You can play KSnakeDuel against the computer or a friend. The aim of the game is to live longer than your opponent. To do that, avoid running into a wall, your own tail and that of your opponent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">KSnakeDuel estas simpla Tron-Klono. Vi povas ludi KSnakeDuel kontraŭ la komputilo aŭ amiko. La celo de la ludo estas vivi pli longe ol via kontraŭulo. Por fari tion, evitu kuri en muron, vian propran voston kaj tiun de via kontraŭulo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KSnakeDuel es un sencillo clon de Tron. Puedes jugar a KSnakeDuel contra la computadora o contra otro oponente. El objetivo del juego es sobrevivir más tiempo que el oponente. Para ello, evita estrellarte contra los muros, tu propia cola y la de tu oponente.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KSnakeDuel on lihtne Troni kloon. Seda saab mängida nii arvuti kui ka sõbra vastu. Mängu siht on püsida elus kauem kui vastane. Selleks tuleb vältida põrkumist seinaga, oma sabaga ja vastasega.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">KSnakeDuel Tron-en klon sinple bat da. KSnakeDuel-en ordenagailuaren aurka edo lagun baten aurka joka dezakezu. Jokoaren xedea zure aurkaria baino luzeago bizirik irautea da. Horretarako, hormarekin, zure isatsarekin eta zure aurkariarenarekin talka egitea ekidin behar duzu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KSnakeDuel on yksinkertainen Tron-klooni. Voit pelata KSnakeDuelia tietokonetta tai kaveria vastaan. Pelin tavoitteena on elää pitempään kuin vastustajasi. Vältä osumasta seiniin, omaan häntääsi tai vastustajaasi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KSnakeDuel est un clone simple du jeu Tron. Vous pouvez jouer à KSnakeDuel contre l'ordinateur ou contre un ami. L'objectif du jeu est de vivre plus longtemps que votre adversaire. Pour ce faire, vous devez éviter d'entrer en collision avec un mur, votre propre queue ou celle de votre adversaire.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KSnakeDuel é un clon simple de Tron. Pódese xogar a KSnakeDuel contra o computador ou contra un amigo. O obxectivo é vivir máis tempo que o adversario. Para o facer, evita bater nunha parede, na túa propia cola ou na do adversario.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">KSnakeDuel הוא שיבוט פשוט של טרון. אפשר לשחק ב־KSnakeDuel נגד המחשב או נגד חבר או חברה. מטרת המשחק היא לשרוד יותר מהיריב. כדי לעשות זאת, יש להימנע מפגיעה בקירות, בזנב של עצמך וביריב.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A KSnakeDuel egy egyszerű Tron-klón. A KSnakeDuelt játszhatja a számítógép vagy egy barátja ellen. A játék célja, hogy tovább éljen, mint az ellenfele. Ehhez el kell kerülnie, hogy falba, saját és ellenfeled farkába fusson.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">KSnakeDuel adalah Tron-Clone sederhana. Kamu bisa memainkan KSnakeDuel melawan komputer atau teman. Tujuan permainan ini adalah untuk hidup lebih lama dari lawanmu. Untuk melakukan itu, hindari berlari ke dinding, ekormu sendiri dan lawanmu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KSnakeDuel è una replica semplice di Tron. Puoi giocare a KSnakeDuel contro il computer o un amico. Lo scopo del gioco è vivere più a lungo del tuo avversario. Per fare questo, evita di sbattere contro il muro, contro la tua coda o quella del tuo avversario.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">KSnakeDuel -ი Tron-ის კლონია. KSnakeDuel შეგიძლიათ როგორც კომპიუტერს, ისე მეგობარს ეთამაშოთ. თამაშის აზრია მეტოქეზე დიდხანს დარჩეთ ცოცხალი. ამის გასაკეთებლად მოერიდეთ შესკდომას კედელთან, თქვენს კუდთან და მეტოქესთან.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KSnakeDuel은 트론 게임 클론입니다. 컴퓨터나 다른 사람과 게임을 즐길 수 있습니다. 게임의 목표는 상대방보다 더 오래 살아남는 것입니다. 벽을 들이받거나, 자기 자신이나 상대방의 궤적을 들이받으면 게임이 끝납니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">„KSnakeDuel“ ir vienkāršs „Tron“ spēles klons. Varat spēlēt „KSnakeDuel“ pret datoru vai draugu. Spēles mērķis ir izdzīvot ilgāk par pretinieku. Lai to izdarītu, izvairieties no sienām un savas un pretinieka astes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KSnakeDuel is een eenvoudig Tron-kloon. U kunt KSnakeDuel spelen tegen de computer of een vriend. Het doel van het spel is langer dan uw tegenstander in leven te blijven. Om dit te bereiken moet u een botsing met een muur, uw eigen staart en de staart van uw tegenstander vermijden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">KSnakeDuel er ein enkel klon av spelet Tron. Du kan spela mot datamaskina eller mot ein venn. Målet er å overleva lenger enn motstandaren, ved å unngå å komma borti veggar, din eigen hale eller halen til motstandaren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KPojedynekWęży jest prostym klonem Tronu. Możesz zagrać w KPojedynekWęży przeciwko komputerowi lub koledze. Celem gry jest przeżycie dłużej niż twój przecinik. Aby to osiągnąć unikaj wpadanie na ściany, swój ogon i ogon przeciwnika.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KSnakeDuel é um clone simples do Tron. Poderá jogar o KSnakeDuel contra o computador ou com um amigo. O objectivo do jogo é sobreviver mais tempo que o seu adversário. Para o fazer, evite bater contra uma parede, a sua própria cauda ou a do seu adversário.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">KSnakeDuel é um clone simples do Tron. Você poderá jogar o KSnakeDuel contra o computador ou contra um amigo. O objetivo é viver mais tempo que o seu adversário. Para fazer isso, evite bater contra uma parede, na sua própria cauda ou na do seu adversário.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">KSnakeDuel — это простой клон «Tron». В KSnakeDuel можно играть против компьютера или с другом. Цель игры заключается в том, чтобы прожить дольше противника. Для этого следует избегать столкновения со стеной, собственным хвостом и противником.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sa">KSnakeDuel इति सरलं Tron-Clone इति । सङ्गणकस्य वा मित्रस्य वा विरुद्धं KSnakeDuel क्रीडितुं शक्नुवन्ति । क्रीडायाः उद्देश्यं भवतः प्रतिद्वन्द्वी अपेक्षया दीर्घकालं जीवितुं भवति। तदर्थं भित्तिं, स्वस्य पुच्छं, प्रतिद्वन्द्वस्य च पुच्छं च परिहरन्तु ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KSnakeDuel je jednoduchý klon Tronu. Môžete ho hrať proti počítaču alebo priateľovi.Cieľom hry je žiť dlhšie ako váš protivník. Na to sa treba vyhýbať stene, vlastnému chvostu a vášmu protivníkovi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KSnakeDuel je preprosti dvojnik igre Tron. Igrate ga lahko proti računalniku ali prijatelju. Cilj igre je, da preživite nasprotnika. Da vam to uspe, se poskusite izogniti trkom s steno ali pa lastnim oz. nasprotnikovim repom.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">К‑змијски-двобој је једноставан клон трона. Можете играти против рачунара или пријатеља. Циљ партије је надживети свог противника. То чините избегавањем судара са зидом, сопственим репом или репом противника.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">K‑zmijski-dvoboj je jednostavan klon trona. Možete igrati protiv računara ili prijatelja. Cilj partije je nadživeti svog protivnika. To činite izbegavanjem sudara sa zidom, sopstvenim repom ili repom protivnika.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">К‑змијски-двобој је једноставан клон трона. Можете играти против рачунара или пријатеља. Циљ партије је надживети свог противника. То чините избегавањем судара са зидом, сопственим репом или репом противника.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">K‑zmijski-dvoboj je jednostavan klon trona. Možete igrati protiv računara ili prijatelja. Cilj partije je nadživeti svog protivnika. To činite izbegavanjem sudara sa zidom, sopstvenim repom ili repom protivnika.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Ormspelet är en enkel klon av Tron. Man kan spela ormspelet mot datorn eller mot en vän. Spelets mål är att överleva längre än motspelaren. För att göra det, undvik att träffa en vägg, din egen kropp eller motspelaren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">K Yılan Düellosu, basit bir Tron klonudur. K Yılan Düellosu'nu bilgisayara veya bir arkadaşınıza karşı oynayabilirsiniz. Oyunun amacı, rakibinizden daha uzun yaşamaktır. Bunu yapmak için bir duvara, kendi kuyruğunuza ve rakibinizin duvarına çarpmayın.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KSnakeDuel — це проста гра «дуель змій» (Tron). Грати у KSnakeDuel можна або з комп’ютерним гравцем, або з другом (подругою). Метою гри є вижити у грі довше, ніж ваш суперник. Щоб зробити це, уникайте контакту зі стінами, хвостом вашої змійки або вашим опонентом.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKSnakeDuel is a simple Tron-Clone. You can play KSnakeDuel against the computer or a friend. The aim of the game is to live longer than your opponent. To do that, avoid running into a wall, your own tail and that of your opponent.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">KSnakeDuel 是 Tron 的简单克隆版。在此游戏中，您可以与电脑或朋友对抗。游戏目标是要比对手的存活时间更长，因此您需要避免撞到墙、自己的尾巴和对手的尾巴。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">KSnakeDuel 是一個簡單的 Tron 複製品。您可以與朋友或電腦對手遊玩 KSnakeDuel。遊戲的目標是比對手活得更久。要生存下去就要避免撞擊到牆壁、自己的軌跡或是對手的軌跡。</p>
  </description>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=ksnakeduel</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=ksnakeduel</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=ksnakeduel&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/ksnakeduel</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://kde.org/images/screenshots/ksnakeduel.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.ksnakeduel.desktop</launchable>
  <provides>
    <binary>ksnakeduel</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="2.1.25081" date="2025-09-11"/>
    <release version="2.1.25080" date="2025-08-14"/>
    <release version="2.1.25043" date="2025-07-03"/>
    <release version="2.1.25042" date="2025-06-05"/>
    <release version="2.1.25041" date="2025-05-08"/>
    <release version="2.1.25040" date="2025-04-17"/>
    <release version="2.1.24123" date="2025-03-06"/>
    <release version="2.1.24122" date="2025-02-06"/>
    <release version="2.1.24121" date="2025-01-09"/>
    <release version="2.1.24120" date="2024-12-12"/>
    <release version="2.1.24083" date="2024-11-07"/>
    <release version="2.1.24082" date="2024-10-10"/>
    <release version="2.1.24081" date="2024-09-12"/>
    <release version="2.1.24080" date="2024-08-22"/>
    <release version="2.1.24052" date="2024-07-04"/>
    <release version="2.1.24051" date="2024-06-13"/>
    <release version="2.1.24050" date="2024-05-23"/>
    <release version="2.1.24022" date="2024-04-11"/>
    <release version="2.1.24021" date="2024-03-21"/>
    <release version="2.1.24020" date="2024-02-28"/>
    <release version="2.1.23085" date="2024-02-15"/>
  </releases>
</component>
